rotoballer.com 2015-06-22

# RotoBaller Privacy Policy | RotoBaller

**RotoBaller Privacy Policies for Inclusion into YardBarker Network (YBN)**

RotoBaller knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers RotoBaller’s treatment of personal information that RotoBaller gathers when you are on the RotoBaller website and when you use RotoBaller services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that RotoBaller does not own or control, or to individuals that RotoBaller does not employ or manage.

Information Collected by RotoBaller

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our RotoBaller users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. RotoBaller and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, RotoBaller cookie information, and the page you requested. RotoBaller uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.  
o RotoBaller may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While RotoBaller will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

E-mail Communications  
RotoBaller is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. RotoBaller may send out e-mails with RotoBaller-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.

Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. RotoBaller cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of RotoBaller’s coolest features.

RotoBaller’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.

Sharing Your Information

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

RotoBaller Personnel: RotoBaller personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of RotoBaller business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if RotoBaller, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

Protection of RotoBaller and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of RotoBaller, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: RotoBaller allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the RotoBaller website.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

Children Under 18 Years of Age

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the RotoBaller website. As a result, RotoBaller does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that RotoBaller has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using RotoBaller or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

RotoBaller may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to thePrivacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the RotoBaller website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit RotoBaller website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 6/13/2013 and last updated 6/13/2013.

**General Privacy Policy  [** **Effective: June 13, 2013]**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which RotoBaller LLC, a limited liability company (“Company”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of its [www.rotoballer.com](http://www.rotoballer.com/) website and any derivative or affiliated websites on which this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, the “Website”). Company reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. You understand that you have the affirmative obligation to check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes, and you hereby agree to periodically review this Privacy Policy for such changes. The continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes an acceptance of those changes.

**Privacy**

Company believes that every User should know how it utilizes the information collected from Users. The Website is not directed at children under 13 years of age, and Company does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age online. Please note that the Website may contain links to other websites. These linked sites may not be operated or controlled by Company. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of these or any other websites, and you access these websites entirely at your own risk. Company recommends that you review the privacy practices of any other websites that you choose to visit.

Company is based, and the Website is hosted, in the United States of America. If User is from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law and User is registering an account on the Website, visiting the Website, purchasing products or services from Company or the Website, or otherwise using the Website, please note that any personally identifiable information that User provides to Company will be transferred to the United States. Any such personally identifiable information provided will be processed and stored in the United States by Company or a service provider acting on its behalf. By providing your personally identifiable information, User hereby specifically and expressly consents to such transfer and processing and the uses and disclosures set forth herein.

**The Information Company Collects**

Users browsing the Website without registering an account or affirmatively providing personally identifiable information to Company do so anonymously. Otherwise, Company may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways. Personally identifiable information may include, without limitation, (i) contact data (such as a User’s name, mailing and e-mail addresses); (ii) demographic data (such as a User’s zip code, age and income); (iii) financial information collected to process purchases made from Company via the Website or otherwise (such as credit card, debit card or other payment information); and (iv) other information requested during the account registration process. If a User communicates with Company by e-mail or otherwise, posts User Content (as defined in the Website Terms of Use) to the Website, posts messages to any forums, completes online forms, surveys or entries or otherwise interacts with or uses the features on the Website, any information provided in such communications may be collected by Company. Company may also collect information about how Users use the Website, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Website, or the domains and IP addresses from which Users originate. While not all of the information that Company collects from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide Company through the Website or otherwise.

Company may use “cookies” or “web beacons” to track how Users use the Website. A cookie is a piece of software that a web server can store on Users’ computers and use to identify Users should they visit the Website again. Users may adjust their web browser software if they do not wish to accept cookies. Company may use third party advertising networks to serve advertisements on the Website. The cookies received with banner advertisements served by these networks are used to collect and build anonymous behavioral profiles by these companies to deliver targeted advertisements and tracking referrals, and Company generally does not have access to this information.

**How Company Uses Information**

Company may use personally identifiable information collected through the Website for the specific purposes for which the information was collected, to process purchases and sales of products or services offered via the Website, to contact Users regarding products and services offered by Company, its parent, subsidiary and other related companies and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and otherwise to enhance Users’ experience with the Website, Company and such affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. Company may also use information collected through the Website for research regarding the effectiveness of the Website and the business planning, marketing, advertising and sales efforts of Company, its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners.

**Disclosure of Information**

Company may share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use with your consent or as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.Company may disclose personally identifiable information at the request of law enforcement or governmental agencies or in response to subpoenas, court orders or other legal process, to establish, protect or exercise Company’s legal or other rights or to defend against a legal claim or as otherwise required or allowed by law. Company may disclose personally identifiable information in order to protect the rights, property or safety of a User or any other person. Company may disclose personally identifiable information to investigate or prevent a violation by User of any contractual or other relationship with Company or the perpetration of any illegal or harmful activity. Company may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from Users to investors and potential partners. Finally, Company may disclose or transfer personally identifiable information collected from Users in connection with or in contemplation of a sale of its assets or business or a merger, consolidation or other reorganization of its business.

**Personal Information Provided as Part of User Content**

If a User includes such User’s personally identifiable information as part of the User Content that such User posts to the Website, such information may be made available to any parties using the Website and/or such User Content. Company does not edit or otherwise remove such information from User Content before it is posted on the Website. If a User does not wish to have such User’s personally identifiable information made available in this manner, such User must remove any such information from the User Content before posting. User contact information (which may include, without limitation, a User’s username and email address) may be included with any User Content that a User posts via the Website. Company is not liable for any damages caused or incurred due to personally identifiable information made available in the foregoing manners.

**Security of Information**

Information about Users that is maintained on Company’s systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and Company cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on or transmitted from its systems will be completely secure. Company is not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures relating to the Website by any Users or third parties.

**Correcting, Updating, Accessing or Removing Personal Information**

If a User’s personally identifiable information changes (such as a User’s zip code), or if a User no longer desires to receive non-account specific information from Company, Company will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update and/or remove that User’s previously-provided personal data. This can be done by emailing a request to Company at [info@rotoballer.com](mailto:info@rotoballer.com?offer_id+15&aff_id=1027) Additionally, you may request access to the personally identifiable information as collected by Company by sending a request to Company as set forth above. Please note that in certain circumstances, Com pany may not be able to completely remove a User’s information from its systems. For example, Company may retain a User’s personal information for legitimate business purposes, if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, for account recovery purposes, if required by law or as retained in Company’s data backup systems or cached or archived pages. All retained personally identifiable information will continue to be subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy to which the User has previously agreed. Please note that you may access and manage your account via the “My Account” link  available on the Website.

**Contacting Company**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, you may contact Company via email: [info@rotoballer.com](mailto:info@rotoballer.com?offer_id+15&aff_id=1027)

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users that are residents of California to request certain information regarding Company’s disclosures of personally identifiable information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. If User is a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact RotoBaller at the above email address.
